<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
>
	<channel>
		<title>Community | Midnight Bard</title>
		<description>RSS</description>		
		<sy:updatePeriod>daily</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<link>http://localhost:4000</link>
		<atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed-community.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
		
   <image>
  <url>/icons/rss.png</url>
  <title>Midnight Bard</title>
  <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
</image>
     
        
        
        
        
		
			
        <item>
  <title>📑LOST (2004)</title>
  <dc:creator>midnightbard</dc:creator>
 <description>
    
        <b>nothing much</b><br/>
                

    
        
            <img style="width:400px; height:400px;" src="https://i.imgur.com/jOtBB1e.png" type="image/jpeg" />
        
    
                 
    <p><em>Mystery, Action &amp; Adventure, Drama</em></p>

<p>Just to give the shortest possible intro - I binged this within a few short weeks, because series is leaving Netflix and I wanted to know how it ends.</p>

<p>I think this would be more fitting to the <em>Opinion</em> category than movies, because I will not ruin your fun by exposing details, so no spoiler alert necessary.</p>

<p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/iQvUAnt.png" class="img-thumbnail" /></p>

<p>In my opinion the first season was great, the rest is a slow-burn torture.</p>

<p>I dislike two of a few main characters, Kate Austen and Jack Shephard so much that I gave them names such as Insect and Parasite, though there were few worse.</p>

<p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/dXaDrlU.png" class="img-thumbnail" /></p>

<p>Just to inform you, this goes on for <strong>118</strong> episodes.</p>

<p>The only characters that gave me any hope and any entertainment were James Sawyer and John Locke, and this has nothing to do with actors.
<img src="https://i.imgur.com/eUNqOvW.png" class="img-thumbnail" /></p>

<hr />

<p>Immediately after this endless torture was over - thankfully in a record time - I jumped into a few episodes of a new season of Wednesday ( which is pale BTW) and I am also watching Colony - which was cancelled, of course - which is NOT on Netflix, of course - which by the way can’t hold me attention, eyelids up or story arc for dear life… of course.</p>
<br/>

    
</description>
  
            
  <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  <link>http://localhost:4000/lost-2004/</link>
  <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/lost-2004/</guid>
</item>


		
			
        <item>
  <title>📑I disapeared for three weeks and this is what I did during that time</title>
  <dc:creator>midnightbard</dc:creator>
 <description>
    
        <b>I disapeared for three weeks and this is what I did during that time</b><br/>
                

    
                 
    <p>During this summer I suddenly disappeared from the grid and this is what I did during that time. I will tell you how I feel but are you really ready for it? ( No.)</p>

<p>I will also say something about all the weird dreams that I am having right now.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>Summary: Facing increasing external pressure and the high cost of third-party software, I initiated an in-house project to develop a more efficient and secure solution. Instead of investing in a costly subscription-based service, I repurposed and rebuilt existing hardware to create a completely custom-built system. This new platform includes a dedicated server (LAMP stack), a tailored social media scheduling tool, and a live-streaming script designed specifically for our needs. The result is a highly secure, cost-effective, and fully customized platform. It eliminates recurring costs, gives us total control over our digital assets, and streamlines our workflow. This project demonstrates the value of internal innovation and resourcefulness. The platform is now live and ready to support our team’s strategic goals.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>At that time I started to experience bigger and bigger pressure onto my work load and things seemed to consist of never-ending obligations, requirements and tasks that seamlessly spiralled into The Forever.</p>

<p>My daughter also forbid any leisure activities, even casual, weekend, or such as smoking, I stopped immediately, no edge, no issues.</p>

<p>That also should be gone in every proximity, or else.</p>

<p>I was also dissatisfied and miffed by everything. 
Also, whatever I did , looked so lame.</p>

<p>Briefly before it I finally torched my old accounts to get rid of my ex companion who was screaming on top of his lungs to come back again, I guess hoping that diabolical non-existent completely simulated and fake situation-ship with my team manager will finally turn things into his advantage.</p>

<p>The only reason that he didn’t burn my house to the ground is because he waits for the closure. 
Also, hope is a bitch. 
And he wants details. 
Also, I think he hoped/hopes I will serve him my ex manager contorted liver arranged with a few women as parsley.</p>

<p>One baby mama. 
Two throwaways. 
Business life is hard. 
Two shots of vodka. 
Repeat.</p>

<p>It was almost impossible to sample in few sentences what exactly he expected. Nor I had time to follow his trail of thoughts, because none of that drunk mental orgy is normal.</p>

<p>I was trying to keep myself busy, and do my favourite things. But, from time to time I would got myself pissed off to the blindness. No metaphor.</p>

<p>The whole internet seemed to be squashed under an ever growing heavy load of AI, unpalatable artificiality that no longer was funny or acceptable.</p>

<p>And in the middle of it - Britain. And inflatables. 
And again my ex protégé waving UK flag - like he cares. 
It’s a lie. He rides a new bitch every season. No metaphor.</p>

<p>And on the other end of success leader there was me,  struggling with the most simplistic tasks - such as sending an update on Bluesky consisting of one liner, a link and a hashtag that might and might not fit into a theme. I don’t know. It has words. It will be good.</p>

<p>Million degrees in shade, the streets were melting outside, in my skull Artic cold. No vibration.</p>

<p>Instead to sit down and have a therapy session, I rearranged the entire apartment and threw a party.</p>

<p>I can easily write a  book, you see - words - but I can’t post a social status. How? I don’t know. How do you decide what is relevant? Is the ultimate expression of yourself, everything you are and all of this, a one liner?</p>

<p>I don’t do many artistic stuff, and this blogging stuff has been pretty much the only creative outlet for my thoughts, if I exclude the YouTube channel which I maintain with other five individuals.</p>

<p>Just to tell you, Troy is so much better writer than I am, I suck.</p>

<p>I am also the driest texter known to humanity and my binary brain doesn’t understand a plethora of so called organic garbage that is yelled by subspecies into a void of empty hollow bucket that internet became during the last few socially inexcusable and disgusting decades.</p>

<p>How many selfies you have on Instagram, by the way? Do you know how many I have? Zero.</p>

<p>If you do selfies than you are a vanity fair, and if you snap boots like me then you are a closeted sadist who walks on people.</p>

<p>I literally feel uneasy readings people thoughts, like poetry, because I feel uninvited and somehow to blame for every misery.</p>

<p>All that reassurance. Why?</p>

<p>So, to reiterate, I was not exactly overwhelmed with love and affections, and certainly nowhere close to spiritually balanced reaction and understanding when I figured out that the same nonsensical, dry conversations devoid of any logic or humanity to be precise - repeat through out various networks ( Threads!!!! ) by the beat of a bot who is hitting that utterly retarded drum.</p>

<p>Thousands upon thousands; I am pretty much a horizontal scroller if you know what I mean, I don’t put much effort into it, but I have a good memory.</p>

<p>I could not possibly compete with the complexity of bots, AI, artificially inflated followers and all that glitz garnished with tits and asses. And how they agree upon so many things and holly shit, sobby rumination with vermillion sourkrauts piled up in the same truck with fake blood sausages, third world alien agendas, herbal life and kosher lamb-fuck.</p>

<p>Probably this animosity against sedated viewpoint of midlife crisis - final form, new me, building yourself, self-improvement , me-time - and all the bruhaha around image, and face, and fitness, and obsession with minimalistic needs, purpose , and self-worth, all that shit I hate,  somehow drove me into the niche the most populated with charlatans who use celeb readings as an ultimate thirst trap for suburban housewives … a despicable online tarot reader.</p>

<p>I don’t hate myself over it, I love it, it is a dream come true, a Satan in the valley of sin.</p>

<p>Nobody, including me myself, could possibly envision me being serious as I am to even to consider it, but here we are. I think it is a very entertaining activity, especially for somebody with huge experience with people … so here we are, my friend Elmo. Elmo is gauging his eyes by the way, because my arm went so up his ass this time, he is laughing by gargling my fingers. He didn’t see it coming. His entire wealth can’t buy him a peace of mind after this.</p>

<p>It is not because you are in this pickle, but he still doesn’t know where is the jar. Ok, back to topic.</p>

<p>Yes, my kind is doing this for centuries, but it doesn’t mean that is my day job, or I would choose this in any scenario. My entire family tree are traders, entrepreneurs, small business owners - so one very out there nation. Nothing relates me with an almost cohesive image of an online tarot reader - a lonely single woman with a pack of cats who has no friends. The only thing I don’t have is time.</p>

<p>I guess Elmo had to arrange for surgery. He had amnesia done.</p>

<p>I don’t plan to retire, but when I figured out I have all things checked, but did I really lived nicely? Like nice. For myself. Did I achieve that ideal of self? Yes, you can live nice, you have cocktails, do business, go shopping, spoil your pets, family and friends … but is there something that is missing? A new challenge? A new big lie I can live, and pretend this theatrics are somehow worth it.</p>

<p>Eternity makes us ambivalent to crisis, after all, there is no way out of this place. 
It has nothing to do with a particular person, place, a space, a Cosmos in total - there is just you with your little thoughts. 
Just me plotting and you cooking me a rue tea.</p>

<p>Anyways, the little things started to bother me - especially the fact that I have so little time for all the hobbies I always wanted to do - writing, drawing, this project, art maybe … maybe just touching grass, go in nature with an old camera and watching birds.</p>

<p>I still didn’t fly my mini drone.</p>

<p>Yes, I know it sounds so plain, but I would really like to draw some nice stuff, or maybe write something fictional - because it sounds so ethereal.</p>

<p>Yes, HAL 3000 has desires.</p>

<p>I also made home made Nutella, a layered cake I always wanted and a lavender cocktail. Isn’t that cute. And it doesn’t have any hidden meaning.</p>

<p>So at the start of summer, my entire stack somehow subtly and without much defence from my end summed down on one single point of absolute SUCKS and that was 5 hours dry tarot live stream followed by trying to produce a status on Threads that nobody actually ever reacted to. That shit was getting old…</p>

<p>And there was this doozy oyster getting million of likes by getting wind up on Instagram…</p>

<p>I am not even doing online tarot for a long time, maybe a year and a half, I have a very cool stuff there, great audience, tips, full monetization, my team, all the help and more that any  individual who does YouTube could ever asked for.</p>

<p>Still… things were not going even close to good, and grass was always greener on the other side, because I also have a burning envy.</p>

<p>Just to note, tech is my vocation so the stuff I created was not exactly too much of an effort, but the circumstances were complicated. When I say complicated, I mean to says psychotic.</p>

<p>First, I was always using mobile connection because of the advantages that is offering. I travel frequently and I don’t need any ground connections anywhere, plus I never saw myself ever as a person who would host anything in my life. This is because I don’t root anywhere.</p>

<p>I didn’t want to be responsible for such a thing, especially not for other people’s data or anything fixed that would work 24/7. That was always something too much to set up… but now the list of advantages that a simplest server would give me were undisputable.</p>

<p>How one such a simple thing can get you so innervated.</p>

<p>Just a solution for a fairly good social media manager to pre-schedule our info posts was quote pricey one, and free versions were offering little to no flexibility or they were missing stuff which I really wanted to have…
Then hosting, website and all that jazz with pre-scheduled streaming and my team having some special demands known only to the other side of madness.</p>

<p>And there is me. I immediately started to complicate, calculate, add stuff that I didn’t really need - for nothing else, but for a simple reason not to even start doing it.</p>

<p>You know I suppose to host a game. 
Naaah!
I feel wrick in my gob at a sheer mention.</p>

<p>I really don’t want to host stuff, not even for internal use. It is a constant pain in an ass, something always breaks. I wanted to spare myself of that fiasco. And doing it. 
Also, a compilation I put together was too expensive in purpose, as always, because I can’t do cheep for dear life of me.</p>

<p>Our current team social manager was super enthusiastic when I mention it, but the only thing that I had stuck into my brain like a lever was our previous manager that was disgusted even by a basic bot I installed into our Discord server. A bot could say hi. That was all that it could do. Birth of Skynet!</p>

<p>So, just an idea to create a full fledged work station didn’t gave me anxiety, it gave me tremors. 
I forgot half of the stuff I needed and another half was hanging in cobwebs and old glory. And, yes, the Skynet.</p>

<p>Fay the other day mention me, you know the game - aw my fucking Gawdus!</p>

<p>Am I too sensitive? I know he had the worst case of bad conscious, but I am just bad, that’s it. No versions to it.</p>

<p>Is it ok to talk in third face?</p>

<p>All that previous stuff made me feel, stupid, inadequate and last century. It’s like saying dump log in full room of front end developers who think that Unity is a Rapture. 
I don’t know if his intention was to retard my self-confidence into recycle bin, but he definitely succeeded. Probably because I was feeding him scripts, which by the way felt ultimately like moisturising a drywall with aloe vera because he was brittle as fuck, a no things didn’t improve after reassurance  - they pulverized. Into a green sludge. And then slowly oozed and stuck half way. 
And now he is hanging there, like a cold bugger half way down the throat.</p>

<p>And all those things served nothing at the end, waste of time, and I was blamed to be slow and late, and it insulted my intelligence, because somehow all the others have better.</p>

<p>Troy told me not to decipher things in that way, but let’s look under the hood of a broken vehicle, isn’t it so, right?</p>

<p>How it could possible be something else.</p>

<p>On the other end I had Penny and Rune who are all in for AI and tech, showing me stuff others did while I was getting smaller and smaller, because those people have it so much  better. I know it is AI, but it looks so good.</p>

<p>I mean they don’t have any expectations, just amazement, but listen… and to be honest the only thing my team wants from me is to be a nice happy person.</p>

<p>I am disgustingly competitive, even when there is no competition; after Penny showed me just one instance of another YouTuber having a glittering glass table I had to have it. I handcrafted the entire thing and in only a few weeks created my own version of it. With sea shells, blitz and everything.</p>

<p>I don’t suffer from this …“normal” standards, but if somebody points me at something, I will not stop until it is done.</p>

<p>Anyways this was a different case, we really needed some sort of a home made brew for our project.</p>

<p>So one day mid July I was coming back home and while walking next to a dumpster I saw somebody had a misfortunate reality check in the world of modern technology, and they didn’t pass.</p>

<p>They divorced from their unfaithful electronic companion, as it was lying in pieces… all over the place.</p>

<p>I think that whoever craft was in question, they probably hit like a pussy because in my case divorce would include more than a fist and shattered panels. 
I mean… I am a gentle delicate flower.</p>

<p>For general information, I can fix anything and patch the most devious handyworks, I also recognise certain authorities when it comes to objects met by walls, floors and other dimensions. Vertical, as well horizontal; by the given appeal it seams this was a man, I would say medium to large.</p>

<p>I guess - I thought to myself while I was dragging misfortunate machine up the staircase - I would not burn anything after all and it is free of charge, the internal content looked promising.</p>

<p>I was watching that box for 2 weeks before I started anything with it. I knew I will fix it in two minutes time, which is not an exaggeration - and I pretended not to have other parts that I need.</p>

<p>I set up LAMP, I created a custom social media manager tool and installed live streamer script for YouTube. Done! It took me three weeks of slow-mo and now I have my black mirror turned triller, journal art bad as an omen and incriminating Inv Ersas Els Alleluies.</p>

<hr />

<p>I also said I will share something about my dreams, they are not the nightmares or anything like that, most of it I forgot or I have a problem re-calling in totality. Parts are missing.</p>

<p>My interest was to figure out the enclosure, as I though it was a unique case. Free range. I had no idea that somebody might be managing that.</p>

<p>The most notable thing is that we all dream or observe the same thing - like the whole group - nothing is done to us, we are almost always just passive observers and things we see are weird.</p>

<p>It is kind of unexpected that all of us suddenly became dream walkers, and we just casually watching other person dreams like it is a TV show.</p>

<p>And this lasts for quite a few months now. It is like an open theatre.</p>

<p>At first the dreams were boring, repetitive, common and then tehy will escalate.</p>

<p>These in question are</p>
<ul>
  <li>violence, of every kind,</li>
  <li>a lot of unalived people,</li>
  <li>sickness and death due to sickness</li>
  <li>bodies, usually a separate body parts, like heads, arms</li>
  <li>dead talking , or them sending correspondence like letters, messages, phone calls</li>
  <li>torture, but the kind you don’t see, like it is almost always done from inside or screams due to the same</li>
  <li>almost subliminal messages - they are right there -  repeated,</li>
  <li>symbols that have no meaning or I can’t find any,</li>
  <li>black obsidian mirrors where people are trapped</li>
  <li>and the town</li>
</ul>

<p>Now a lot of people dream the same from time to time, but not a lot of people dream the same simultaneously and communicate in so called dream.</p>

<p>I already talked to people, my friends in a dream while we both could recognise a said conversation from a dream when we would wake up. Especially with a people I am bound or with my closest people. That is not an issue.</p>

<p>But, the space or a place we all visit, usually had us going on with something on  different locations, or we briefly communicated and the next day morning the exchange was interesting.</p>

<p>It was like we were visiting Narnia, but it was not that kind of a place. We also had tasks, jobs or some sort of education going on.</p>

<p>fay was the first one to describe a place where she was sent to pass some tests, and it was wicked.</p>

<p>Then I suspected maybe because one of us stuck in situation ship, we all have shared experiences with something popular called liminal spaces, back rooms, yellow rooms etc etc.</p>

<p>It was not that. We already described a place to each other, at first it looked remotely as an Island - that island , isolation - but at one point I investigated further and found out that there is this big town in that place.</p>

<p>People are weird, there are a lot of technology included, very tall spires, black almost obsidian black skyscrapers, and sky was odd, purple or just extremely strong blue colour. I saw no sun.  Sunshine is there.</p>

<p>Then my companions confirm that they saw the same and this comedy continued for months. Living there, and then back here.</p>

<p>Then I, by pure curiosity, searched for a mystical town with spires and black skyscrapers on TikTok and it came out as Birignan. It is a local legend in Philippines, I thought nothing of it. Then I found Skypea, then Avalon and … so on… so fort… it seems that a town with a list of things we all saw exists in every single culture all the way back to Hyperboria.</p>

<p>There are other mystical towns before that but they are more part of a creation story, and do not fit description.</p>

<p>You can investigate all about these things; I guess a lot of people had all sort of visions of dreams, but this is the fist time I ever heard a whole community moved into a loony town. 
It seems that because one of us stuck there, we all go there or we are all somehow involved.</p>

<p>Well, I thought to myself, if we somehow just appear there, maybe that place has some sort of an exit or entrance, somebody to go in and out, as those things were described .</p>

<p>For example in Avalon you have boats, I think Hyperboria same or similar something, some vessel, but all these places appear randomly and are protected by magic. So, how exactly we get inside? Or out? I know we are from the other side, but I had absolutely no idea, I was not under impression that would include Hyperboria.</p>

<p>So while I was inside I looked for some sort of an entrance, but it was not there, and by the way it was very hard to define if a place is an island or something else. Then I looked for a mean - like a boat. Then I thought maybe it is a bridge. It symbolically connects two sides.</p>

<p>I found a road bridge, just a bridge. There was a semi arch there, and something that looked like a phone , an open phone booth, no phone, just plate.</p>

<p>I stood there and at one moment there was this huge silent truck, a road train slid into that bridge, no or very little sound, white inside and outside and a driver was this common guy , also dressed in common white trousers, tshirt, he asked me where to, I said outside of here, drive me to … I don’t know, Andorra - he picked me up, I fell asleep immediately when I entered, and the next thing I know he is saying we are here, get out.</p>

<p>I get out and I am in the town, it is allegedly a main town of Andorra. He drives silently, no disturbance. I mean he is driving a truck. 
It doesn’t look familiar, I visit a shopping centre, walk around, briefly after that I woke up.</p>

<p>I informed Fay about what I saw in my dream, she said no crap, we check the Andorra thing - I mean there is nothing there, it is a desolation - and ho and behold, that’s the place. That’s the town. That’s the exact shopping mall.</p>

<p>And Fay says she remembers being here, she describes a shop, we find it and that is the same shop.</p>

<p>Ok, anyways, next time we go together, you wait me on an island. Fay says ok. Next opportunity with that bridge I say to the driver take me to the island.</p>

<p>Now, I don’t think he understood what island, because I asked to take me to The Island, like a captive one.</p>

<p>I got out, I realize where he took me, but Fay was there, truck leaves silently like before, we visit a shopping mall, a house and kind of phase out though all of that into that nothingness and wake up.</p>

<p>Back in reality, we visit Google maps and all that jazz. Yup, a place is there. With all details. Which we by the way don’t know.</p>

<p>I never had an issue to understand that our auras can travel with a strong connection somehow, but how come one single person can take you there from a place that suppose to be in between?</p>

<p>I am still thinking about this and we had conversation with many of these individuals there, they don’t see us like a foreign population. If you are from the other side, you are considered domestic.</p>

<p>Now all of that would be fine and dandy, if we didn’t attend their classes their. Allegedly they give classes to behave more confused I guess…or more humans, just from the other side human. Or this side. So essentially an extra classes for shapeshifters.</p>

<p>I will give you just a few small details … they for example keep demons as pets. Pets. No danger for ones health whatsoever. Which is giga chad.</p>

<p>Next. Is there any humans, like here humans there? Yes. But they are either lost, believing they live a life or they are in hell.</p>

<p>For example this school of stupid they have - I was constantly standing up to proclaim something illogical and simply not profitable in any way, and a speaker was always like - yes, but this is how THEY do it, or feel it. This is how they see it.</p>

<p>We also had exams. And they are super weird. Essentially you get a person or a whole situation-ship wherein they are. And the exam is constructed by affinity, so not all of us get the same. So, you can end up in … persistence training, or in target practice where you die until you get a hold of it - I guess how to die while not screaming too loud.</p>

<p>So, this time we kind of ended up in social studies, which was hard to watch.</p>

<p>You would get for starters just a human and his brain, and then you would need to describe what he is going though. And you would phase thought all of that, possibly causing an individual horrific visuals.</p>

<p>And for the record , none of this was done to a normal decent humans, or samples , aw no. 
People who were in this school - for skinwalkers - were the ones who betrayed their own dimension.</p>

<p>There was another test where we were told we will do life, and I was great, this is my thing. But, the problem is we are not the one who is doing life.</p>

<p>You get a small cart with some sort of a control panel where you choose settings for … lifing I guess. And you can also communicate with others during that test, it is not consider cheating, and you have a life that includes a human and his space. A person believes that it is a life, you can be a participant, you don’t need to. But everything is rigged. And your exam consists of managing the settings correctly. Not helping, not advising, just managing the settings of life.</p>

<p>Long story short, we basically almost failed, Fay crashed her cart, I tried to assist my subject … and it was terrible.</p>

<p>Anyways, I have a little different view now on the case with island enclosure. It is not what I thought it is.</p>

<p>Continuation follows …</p>
<br/>

    
</description>
  
            
  <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  <link>http://localhost:4000/summer/</link>
  <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/summer/</guid>
</item>


		
	</channel>
</rss>