<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
>
	<channel>
		<title>Technology | Midnight Bard</title>
		<description>RSS</description>		
		<sy:updatePeriod>daily</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<link>http://localhost:4000</link>
		<atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed-technology.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
		
   <image>
  <url>/icons/rss.png</url>
  <title>Midnight Bard</title>
  <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
</image>
     
        
        
        
        
		
			
        <item>
  <title>📑LAMP home server and other things</title>
  <dc:creator>midnightbard</dc:creator>
 <description>
    
        <b>A few stuff about home server, intranet and social media scheduler</b><br/>
                

    
        
            <img style="width:400px; height:400px;" src="https://i.imgur.com/JfaKi81.png" type="image/jpeg" />
        
    
                 
    <p>I revamped a discarded PC and installed LAMP on it. It is a home server, which means no hosting online due to the nature of my connection ( mobile) but I can build it into anything for personal use.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>A LAMP server is a popular open-source web development platform that combines four key components: <strong>L</strong>inux, <strong>A</strong>pache, <strong>M</strong>ySQL, and <strong>P</strong>HP. It provides a complete and reliable environment for hosting websites and web applications. The four components work together to deliver web content: Linux as the operating system, Apache as the web server, MySQL for database management, and PHP for server-side scripting.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>Years ago I worked on WordPress so I installed that and Piwigo. Personally I think WordPress is enough due to extensive plugins and options.</p>

<p>The only thing it missed, to be an absolute solution for my in-house tool for me and my team - is a social media post scheduler. All available tools were either paid or limited, and most of them don’t have all networks I am interested to include into our project.</p>

<p>So, I built that part on my own, and for now it schedules posts for Bluesky, Mastodon, Threads, Tumblr and Discord.</p>

<p>The hardest part to make was Threads; Meta programming ( Facebook ) significantly changed from the time I was working on it.</p>

<p>Anyways I created a working program for other four in a day, and the next day I needed to learn and figure out how Threads suppose to work.</p>

<p>I needed an extra day to polish a front end design, adjust it to mobile template, and to install additional scripts for extra features - buttons, calendar, draft posts and some quirks etc etc.</p>

<p>Today the whole thing had a fall-out because of the unstable network conditions and glitches due to - I guess - solar flares. They reported we had five in a row and that it MIGHT disrupt some things.</p>

<p>That was a great opportunity to install additional safety measurements, so that cron doesn’t fall out of a key, and all of it works smoothly and without glitches.</p>

<p>Glitches will happen , because this is a server side website and Rune ( my neighbour who is a social media manager) is using it on a home connection.</p>

<p>Yes, I established a sort of a intranet, and yes my team already asked if it can host games and other, more profound tools, like 3D modelling…</p>

<p>Rune used to work with Buffer and he was used to have a database of drafts, so I built an additional page for that as well, with search, colour coded networks, edits … etc…</p>

<p>Buffer also has a calendar view, so I made an extra widget with that too.</p>

<p>Anyways, an app is very simple and this is how it looks like ( for now):</p>

<h4 id="dashboard">Dashboard</h4>

<p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/JfaKi81.png" class="img-thumbnail" /></p>

<h4 id="new-post-scheduler">New post scheduler</h4>

<p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/HD43SKg.png" class="img-thumbnail" /></p>

<h4 id="calendar-view">Calendar view</h4>

<p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/Z8KhJuR.png" class="img-thumbnail" /></p>

<h4 id="drafts">Drafts</h4>

<p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/FFFPbup.png" class="img-thumbnail" /></p>

<p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/t4hSBtc.png" class="img-thumbnail" /></p>

<hr />

<p>I will make sure that all this works smoothly, and then additionally probably some time next month I will upgrade it for TikTok and Pinterest.</p>

<hr />
<br/>

    
</description>
  
            
  <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  <link>http://localhost:4000/lamp-home-server/</link>
  <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/lamp-home-server/</guid>
</item>


		
			
        <item>
  <title>📑YouTube streaming from home server</title>
  <dc:creator>midnightbard</dc:creator>
 <description>
    
        <b>A few words about broadcast, a prerecorded live stream for YouTube</b><br/>
                

    
        
            <img style="width:400px; height:400px;" src="https://i.imgur.com/Sic4yV7.png" type="image/jpeg" />
        
    
                 
    <p>There is more than one reason why I wanted a home server, and it is not only for team organization and social media scheduler - which also turned out to be great to have.</p>

<p>With home server I can stream my content - it is not a live stream, better word would be a broadcast.</p>

<p>A script is very simple and needs only a few tweaks on YouTube; well, so far what I managed to put together for a simple purpose of advertising my tarot service. So, that is for a start. Later I will use it for more than just that one thing.</p>

<p>I tried with video premiere with chat, but it didn’t get much of a traction, so I opted for a full fledged stream solution.</p>

<p>First, a video.</p>

<p>I created a video that will serve as an info for my service, it is very short, a few minutes, a few static images for decoration at the end of a video.</p>

<p>Then I shrink it with a Handbrake and uploaded into a video folder on my server.</p>

<p>Second, a script with cron job.</p>

<p>Script defines what is happening with a video and cron when it will run. I decided to loop my video and to start running it late at night when I am usually already sleeping.</p>

<p>Third, YouTube settings.</p>

<p>My script needs link, key and settings for auto start and stop in my live stream Studio to be on.</p>

<p>So broadcast will be started by a timer in cron, and once a loop is done, a live broadcast will shut down.</p>

<hr />

<p>Future plan is to produce list of small videos and to create a whole night entertaining program and then run it on days I find appropriate.</p>

<p>Live streams that have chat available for customers will be moderated by Penny, as all this is happening inside of her time zone while I sleep.</p>

<hr />

<br/>

    
</description>
  
            
  <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  <link>http://localhost:4000/youtube-streaming-from-home-server/</link>
  <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/youtube-streaming-from-home-server/</guid>
</item>


		
	</channel>
</rss>