<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
>
	<channel>
		<title>Community | Midnight Bard</title>
		<description>RSS</description>		
		<sy:updatePeriod>daily</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<link>http://localhost:4000</link>
		<atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed-community.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
		
   <image>
  <url>/icons/rss.png</url>
  <title>Midnight Bard</title>
  <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
</image>
     
        
        
        
        
		
			
        <item>
  <title>📑LOST (2004)</title>
  <dc:creator>midnightbard</dc:creator>
 <description>
    
        <b>nothing much</b><br/>
                

    
        
            <img style="width:400px; height:400px;" src="https://i.imgur.com/jOtBB1e.png" type="image/jpeg" />
        
    
                 
    <p><em>Mystery, Action &amp; Adventure, Drama</em></p>

<p>Just to give the shortest possible intro - I binged this within a few short weeks, because series is leaving Netflix and I wanted to know how it ends.</p>

<p>I think this would be more fitting to the <em>Opinion</em> category than movies, because I will not ruin your fun by exposing details, so no spoiler alert necessary.</p>

<p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/iQvUAnt.png" class="img-thumbnail" /></p>

<p>In my opinion the first season was great, the rest is a slow-burn torture.</p>

<p>I dislike two of a few main characters, Kate Austen and Jack Shephard so much that I gave them names such as Insect and Parasite, though there were few worse.</p>

<p><img src="https://i.imgur.com/dXaDrlU.png" class="img-thumbnail" /></p>

<p>Just to inform you, this goes on for <strong>118</strong> episodes.</p>

<p>The only characters that gave me any hope and any entertainment were James Sawyer and John Locke, and this has nothing to do with actors.
<img src="https://i.imgur.com/eUNqOvW.png" class="img-thumbnail" /></p>

<hr />

<p>Immediately after this endless torture was over - thankfully in a record time - I jumped into a few episodes of a new season of Wednesday ( which is pale BTW) and I am also watching Colony - which was cancelled, of course - which is NOT on Netflix, of course - which by the way can’t hold me attention, eyelids up or story arc for dear life… of course.</p>
<br/>

    
</description>
  
            
  <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
  <link>http://localhost:4000/lost-2004.md/</link>
  <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/lost-2004.md/</guid>
</item>


		
	</channel>
</rss>